{
  "1": {
    "Quiz Type": "AQI",
    "Question": "What does AQI represent?",
    "Correct Answer": "Air Quality Index",
    "Option1": "Air Quality Information",
    "Option2": "Air Quiz Information",
    "Option3": "Accurate Air Information",
    "Reason": "AQI is the abbreviate for Air Quality Index"
  },
  "2": {
    "Quiz Type": "Ozone Effects",
    "Question": "The climate is very warm today and Sam wants to go out for a football match. Do you think he should go out?",
    "Correct Answer": "No, he should stay home",
    "Option1": "Yes, he should go out",
    "Option2": "Maybe",
    "Option3": "Yes, he should go out and also take his friends along to cheer him",
    "Reason": "Ozone level is higher in warmer climate so it is adviced that children should stay indoor"
  },
  "3": {
    "Quiz Type": "Ozone Sources",
    "Question": "What is the correct abbreviate for Ozone",
    "Correct Answer": "O3",
    "Option1": "O2",
    "Option2": "O4",
    "Option3": "O",
    "Reason": "The correct abbreviate for Ozone is O3"
  },
  "4": {
    "Quiz Type": "AQI",
    "Question": "The Air Quality Index is between 0-50. Do you think you should go out?",
    "Correct Answer": "Yes",
    "Option1": "No",
    "Option2": "Maybe",
    "Option3": "I don't know",
    "Reason": "Air quality between 0-50 is satisfactory and poses little or no health risk"
  },
  "5": {
    "Quiz Type": "AQI",
    "Question": "The Air Quality Index is between 51-100. Do you think you should go out?",
    "Correct Answer": "Maybe",
    "Option1": "Yes",
    "Option2": "No",
    "Option3": "I don't know",
    "Reason": "Air quality between AQI 51-100 is acceptable but the pollution range is high."
  },
  "6": {
    "Quiz Type": "AQI",
    "Question": "The Air Quality Index is between 101-150. Do you think you should go out?",
    "Correct Answer": "Maybe",
    "Option1": "Yes",
    "Option2": "No",
    "Option3": "I don't know",
    "Reason": "Air quality between AQI 101-150 is harmful for children, people with lung cancer and older adults"
  },
  "7": {
    "Quiz Type": "AQI",
    "Question": "The Air Quality Index is between 151-200. Do you think we should go out?",
    "Correct Answer": "No",
    "Option1": "Yes",
    "Option2": "Maybe",
    "Option3": "I don't know",
    "Reason": "Air quality between AQI 151-200 affects everyone and it is adviced that only go out if it is necessary"
  },
  "8": {
    "Quiz Type": "AQI",
    "Question": "The Air Quality Index is between 201-300. Do you think we should go out?",
    "Correct Answer": "No",
    "Option1": "Yes",
    "Option2": "Maybe",
    "Option3": "I don't know",
    "Reason": "Air quality between AQI 201-300 causes an serious health effect"
  },
  "9": {
    "Quiz Type": "AQI",
    "Question": "The Air Quality Index is above 300. Do you think you should go out?",
    "Correct Answer": "No",
    "Option1": "Yes",
    "Option2": "Maybe",
    "Option3": "I don't know",
    "Reason": "Air quality over AQI 300 is most dangeours and no one should go out"
  },
  "10": {
    "Quiz Type": "Ozone Sources",
    "Question": "Ozone formation increase due to",
    "Correct Answer": "Heat and Sunlight",
    "Option1": "Water droplets",
    "Option2": "Wind",
    "Option3": "Autumn",
    "Reason": "Ozone formation is higher in warmer months"
  },
  "11": {
    "Quiz Type": "Ozone Sources",
    "Question": "Which time of the day would ozone level be at peak",
    "Correct Answer": "Afternoon",
    "Option1": "Morning",
    "Option2": "Night",
    "Option3": "Evening",
    "Reason": "Ozone level is highest in the afternoon"
  },
  "12": {
    "Quiz Type": "AQI",
    "Question": "Why is it impotant for you to known the AQI level",
    "Correct Answer": "",
    "Option1": "",
    "Option2": "",
    "Option3": "",
    "Reason": ""
  },
  "13": {
    "Quiz Type": "Ozone Sources",
    "Question": "Where is Ozone found?",
    "Correct Answer": "Air",
    "Option1": "Water",
    "Option2": "Soil",
    "Option3": "Fire",
    "Reason": "Ozone is a gas present in the Air we breathe"
  },
  "14": {
    "Quiz Type": "Ozone Effects",
    "Question": "When the air is unhealty what should we do?",
    "Correct Answer": "",
    "Option1": "",
    "Option2": "",
    "Option3": "",
    "Reason": ""
  },
  "15": {
    "Quiz Type": "AQI",
    "Question": "AQI is betweeen 0-50. Canyou guess the Color for this range?",
    "Correct Answer": "Green",
    "Option1": "Blue",
    "Option2": "Yellow",
    "Option3": "Pink",
    "Reason": "AQI between 0-50 is represented by Green colour"
  },
  "16": {
    "Quiz Type": "AQI",
    "Question": "AQI is betweeen 51-100. Canyou guess the Color for this range?",
    "Correct Answer": "Yellow",
    "Option1": "Green",
    "Option2": "Orange",
    "Option3": "Red",
    "Reason": "AQI between 51-100 is represented by Yellow colour"
  },
  "17": {
    "Quiz Type": "AQI",
    "Question": "AQI is betweeen 101-150. Canyou guess the Color for this range?",
    "Correct Answer": "Orange",
    "Option1": "Green",
    "Option2": "Yellow",
    "Option3": "Blue",
    "Reason": "AQI between 101-150 is represented by Orange colour"
  },
  "18": {
    "Quiz Type": "AQI",
    "Question": "AQI is betweeen 151-200. Canyou guess the Color for this range?",
    "Correct Answer": "Red",
    "Option1": "Yellow",
    "Option2": "Orange",
    "Option3": "Purple",
    "Reason": "AQI between 151-200 is represented by Red colour"
  },
  "19": {
    "Quiz Type": "AQI",
    "Question": "AQI is betweeen 201-300. Canyou guess the Color for this range?",
    "Correct Answer": "Purple",
    "Option1": "Yellow",
    "Option2": "Maroon",
    "Option3": "Red",
    "Reason": "AQI between 201-300 is represented by Purple colour"
  },
  "20": {
    "Quiz Type": "AQI",
    "Question": "AQI is betweeen 301-500-. Canyou guess the Color for this range?",
    "Correct Answer": "Maroon",
    "Option1": "Green",
    "Option2": "Red",
    "Option3": "Purple",
    "Reason": "AQI between 301-500 is represented by Maroon colour"
  },
  "21": {
    "Quiz Type": "Ozone Effects",
    "Question": "Which vitamin should you consume more to protect yourself from Ozone",
    "Correct Answer": "Vitamin C and E",
    "Option1": "Vitamin A and B",
    "Option2": "Vitamin C and D",
    "Option3": "Vitamin B and D",
    "Reason": "People who consume low amount of vitamin C and E are at higher risk to expose to ozone"
  },
  "22": {
    "Quiz Type": "Ozone Effects",
    "Question": "Do you think Ozone effects the ecosystem?",
    "Correct Answer": "Yes",
    "Option1": "No",
    "Option2": "Maybe",
    "Option3": "I don't know",
    "Reason": "Ozone affects sensitive vegetation and ecosystems, including forests, parks, wildlife refuges and wilderness areas"
  },
  "23": {
    "Quiz Type": "Ozone Effects",
    "Question": "When Ozone enters a sensitive plant it can?",
    "Correct Answer": "Slow the growth of the plant",
    "Option1": "The plants grows raipdly",
    "Option2": "The plants starts to bloom",
    "Option3": "I don't know",
    "Reason": "When a sufficient amount of Ozone gas enters a plant it slows the growth of the plant"
  },
  "24": {
    "Quiz Type": "Ozone Effects",
    "Question": "Can Ozone irritate the lining of the nose, airways and lungs?",
    "Correct Answer": "Yes",
    "Option1": "No",
    "Option2": "Maybe",
    "Option3": "I don't know",
    "Reason": "Yes Ozone can irritate the lining of the nose, airways and lungs"
  }
}